all right I'm just going to make a
really quick video just to let you know
that you cannot stream from the Planet
Fitness Wi-Fi in fact you can't work
from the Planet Fitness Wi-Fi I got 466
megabits per second so the bit rate was
like way too l i mean I figured it would
be I figured it would be really bad but
I wanted to make a a video blog just to
update for anybody else who's thinking
about digital noad lifestyle I did
however get the mic done I got it all
set up it's on a nice boom I can control
and everything uh it's probably going to
mess with the bubble shot I don't know
should we check it should we see should
we see if it's going to mess with the
bubble shot let's take a
peek uh bubble shot is still there hey
look it actually got rid of the mic so
it does look pretty weird but it's going
to be doable so that is all that's all
just a really quick video just to let
you
know what's up wait what did I do did I
go to the wrong thing oh supposed to go
back to car Studio there we go
so that's a thumbs up a Thumb Thumbs Up
no that's a thumbs down thumbs down
thumbs
down also according to Planet Fitness I
found out you can actually stream from
inside of Planet Fitness you just
absolutely cannot have any camera on any
person so uh you know it's 25 bucks a
month to me get a membership Planet
Fitness you can go take your shower you
can go do whatever A lot of people who
do van life and car camping that's what
they do they've been doing it for a long
time this is no new information but I
did want to put it out there for a few
of you that wanted to get it published
all right that's all